In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to make the W sound.
我们将学习如何发出W音。
To make this sound, wuh,
要发出这个音，wuh，
the lips form a tight circle.
嘴唇形成一个紧密的圆圈。
Wuh.
Wuh。
The back part of the tongue stretches up towards the soft palate,
舌头的后部向软腭伸展，
while the front part of the tongue lightly touches the back of the bottom front teeth.
而舌头的前部轻轻触碰下前牙的后面。
To give this sound the right quality,
为了使这个音质正确，
you have to close the vocal cords to get this sound, wuh, wuh,
你必须闭合声带来发出这个音，wuh，wuh，
wuh, which we add to the sound, wuh.
wuh，我们将其添加到音中，wuh。
You release the vocal cords as you release the lips coming out of the W sound, wuh.
当你从W音中释放嘴唇时，释放声带。
Let's look at the sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个音。
With the tight circle for the lips,
嘴唇形成紧密的圆圈，
you can't see the tongue at all,
你完全看不到舌头，
but it lifts in the back.
但它在后部抬起。
The word Y,
单词Y，
a tight circle for the lips.
嘴唇形成紧密的圆圈。
The word West,
单词West，
again, a tight circle for the lips.
再次，嘴唇形成紧密的圆圈。
The word unwind.
单词unwind。
Here,
这里，
the W is in the middle of the word.
W在单词的中间。
We still take the time to bring the lips into a tight circle.
我们仍然花时间将嘴唇形成一个紧密的圆圈。
This sound is most common at the beginning of words.
这个音最常见于单词的开头。
It doesn't occur at the end of any words,
它不会出现在任何单词的结尾，
though the letter W does.
尽管字母W会。
The W consonant.
W辅音。
Unwind.
Unwind。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Water.
Water。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Water.
Water。
Welcome.
Welcome。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Welcome.
Welcome。
Rework.
Rework。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Rework.
Rework。
Away.
Away。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Away.
Away。
Between.
Between。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Between.
Between。
Will.
Will。
Wuh.
Wuh。
Will.
Will。